Guide to the Papers of Richard Phillips Feynman, 1933-1988
Archives
- Group I
  - Section V: Manuscripts
    - Lecture Notes for Courses
      - Quantum Electrodynamics and Meson Theories (at CIT) (folder 5) 1950; (folder 6) 1953 (Box 8, Folder Folders 5-6)
      - Statistical Mechanics and Kinetic Theory (at Cornell) (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Fenômenos no Estado Sólido 1963 (in Brazil) (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Physics Course, no title (Feynman ?) (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Lectures on Elementary Physics (folder 2) 1962; (folder 3) Physics IB notes, 1962; (folder 4) Physics IC notes, 1962 (Box 9, Folder Folders 2-4)
      - Lectures on Gravitation 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Physics Course, Miscellaneous Notes, Exam Questions; Grade Book ca 1950 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence re: Physics
      - Curriculum 1962-1966 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Lectures on Physics (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Physics Problems (folder 3) 1946-1964; (folder 4) 1965- 1966; (folder 5) 1967-1968; (folder 6) 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder Folders 3-6)
    - Notes and Calculations
      - Density Fluctuations in Fermi Gas (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Dirac Equation (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Energy Levels of a Self-Interacting Atom, etc. (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Groups and Quantum Mechanics (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Harmonic Oscillators (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Helium (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Mathematical Functions and Self-Interacting Atom (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Mesons, Cosmic Rays (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Born Approximation of Yukama Potential (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Meson Interaction (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Meson Theory (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Vector Charged Mesons (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Particles (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Phage (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Quantum Electrodynamics (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Radiationless Scattering (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Sedimentation (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - "Space-Time Approach to Quantum Electrodynamics" (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Superconductivity (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder Folders 10-11)
      - Theory of Positrons; Self-Energy in an Atom; Radiation Scattering; Spreading Dirac Packet (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - WKB Approximation to Dirac Equation (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous Notes (6 folders) (Box 13, Folder Folders 3-8)
    - Miscellaneous Manuscripts
      - Preprints of others, including notes and correspondence (5 folders) (Box 14, Folder Folders 1-5)
      - Codes (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Notes related to MIT senior thesis (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - MIT senior thesis 1939 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - PhD thesis MSS (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder Folders 3-4)
      - Notes, University of Michigan Summer Symposium, from W. Nierenberg:
      - Untitled 1947 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - "Quantum Electrodynamics," by Julian Schwinger 1948 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - "A New Approach to Quantum Electro- dynamics," by Feynman, taken by M. Fuchs and R. Riddell 1949 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Early MSS on Quantum Electrodynamics [n.d., post-1948] (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Untitled MS, typewritten 1951 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Notebooks
      - "The Calculus for the Practical Man" ca 1933 (photocopy; original in Niels Bohr Library, American Institute of Physics) (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - High School Trigonometry and Advanced Algebra 1933 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Notebook ca 1933 and later (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Notebook of letters between Feynman and Theodore A. Welton 1935-1939 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - "Notebook of Things I Don't Know About" 1940 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Notebook ca 1960: Biochemical Techniques re RNA and DNA; "Mutual Suppression of r Mutants of Bacteriophage T4D," note from Bob [Sinsheimer] (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Notebook [n.d.]: Quantum Electrodynamics; "The Present Situation in Quantum Electrodynamics," Solvay Conference 1961; memo, J. W. M. DuMond to Feynman, 27 January 1955, "Anomalous Magnetic Moment of the Electron;" other loose notes (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Section VI: Biographical
    - Personal Correspondence
      - Mary Louise Bell 1951-56 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Misc. Personal Correspondence 1943-1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Photographs (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Biographical Information (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Awards
      - Einstein Award 1954 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - E. O. Lawrence Award 1962 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Nobel Prize: See: Group 2, Section II
      - National Academy of Sciences, Diploma of Election to Fellow, 27 April 1954 See: Group 2, Section X, Oversize
      - Venice Nobel Prize Scroll, 5 February 1958 See: Group 2, Section X, Oversize
  - Section VII: Audio And Video Material
    - BBC programs:
      - BBC-Horizons: "The Pleasure of Finding Things Out" 1982 (3/4" videotape); "Fun to Imagine" 1983 (2 3/4" videotapes) (Box 19)
    - Interview on "Viewpoint," KNXT TV, conducted by Bill Stout, ca 1957-1965 (audio cassette) (Box 19)
    - Feynman speaking at Far Rockaway High School, ca late 1960s (audio cassette) (Box 19)
    - Drum music from India: tape from Hildegard Lamfrom (Box 19)
    - "The Structure of the Proton," 10 May 1973 (3 videotapes in V-32 format) (Box 20)
- Group II
  - Section I: Correspondence
    - Declinations
      - 1972-73 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - 1974-75 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - 1976-79 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - 1980-82 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - 1983 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - 1984 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - 1985 Jan-July (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - 1985 Aug-Dec (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - 1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - 1987 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Addison-Wesley, Feynman Lectures on Physics
      - General correspondence 1964-68 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Requests for copies, problem sets, etc. 1964-71 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Corrections and additions 1964, 1975-76 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Exercise Book 1964 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Copyright clearances (Edward Ansell) 1984 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Foreign editions 1964-88 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Requests for permissions 1964-85 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Reviews 1967-68 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Addison-Wesley--W. A. Benjamin, Inc., Statistical Mechanics 1972-86 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - American Institute of Physics, Interview with C. Weiner, correspondence 1975-86 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - American Scientist 1973 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Aspect, Alain 1984 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - A misc (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - A. T. & T. 1987 (Box 22)
      - Abbott, Richard L. 1975 (Box 22)
      - Ackerman, Diane 1979 (Box 22)
      - Akerlof, Carl W. 1981 (Box 22)
      - Allen, Robert F., Jr. 1981 (Box 22)
      - Alumni Association, CIT 1983 (Box 22)
      - Alvarez, Luis W. 1979 See also: Section II, Nobel Prize (Box 22)
      - Amati, D. 1976 (Box 22)
      - American Association for the Advancement of Science 1974 (Box 22)
      - Andersen, Bjorn 1976 (Box 22)
      - Andrade, P. da R. 1972 (Box 22)
      - Andrews, Mildred, Fund 1987 (Box 22)
      - Andronikashvili, E. L. 1974 See also: Petrac, Dusan (Box 22)
      - Angelidis, T. D. 1977 (Box 22)
      - Arlick, Alfred B. 1972 (Box 22)
      - Arth, Michael E. 1986 (Box 22)
      - Ashkin, Julius and Claire 1984 (Box 22)
      - Aspden, Harold 1974 (Box 22)
      - Aspen Center for Physics 1978 (Box 22)
      - Associated Students of Caltech 1982 (Box 22)
      - Augousti, Andy 1982 (Box 22)
      - Auno [?], Shigeyuki 1988 (Box 22)
      - Ayers, R. D. 1976 (Box 22)
      - Ayres, Herbert F. 1984 See also: Section VIII, Unsolicited manuscripts (Box 22)
      - Anonymous 1983, n.d. (Box 22)
    - Benjamin, W. A., Inc.
      - General Correspondence 1962-74 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence (includes Benjamin/Cummings Publishing Co.) 1976-84 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Photon-Hadron Interactions 1972 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Bethe, Hans 1965-66, 1975, 1978, 1983 See also: Section II, Nobel Prize (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Birkhäuser Boston Inc., RPF Collected Works 1982-83 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Bjorken, James D. 1978-79 See also: Section VIII (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Blackmarr, Philip 1979-85 See also: Section VIII (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Bohm, David 1976 See also: Routledge and Kegan Paul (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Bohr, Aage and family 1974-79 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Bohr, Niels, Institute 1978 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Bogazici University See: Hacinliyan, Avadis
    - British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) (folder 11) 1964-68; (folder 12) 1973-87; (folder 13) "The Hunting of the Quark" (script and notes) [1974?] (folder 14) "The Pleasure of Finding Things Out" (script) 1981 See also: Cornell University, Messenger Lectures (Box 23, Folder Folders 11-14)
    - B misc (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Baca, Rosemary 1980 (Box 23)
      - Bader, Richard 1978 (Box 23)
      - Bate, Edward R. 1980 (Box 23)
      - Bateman Eichler 1979 (Box 23)
      - Belcher, Harold H. 1974 (Box 23)
      - Bentley, Robert 1987 (Box 23)
      - Bergman, Merle n.d. and 1984 (Box 23)
      - Berliner, Elena 1974 (Box 23)
      - Billig, Marin 1975 (Box 23)
      - Biofuel, Inc. 1979 (Box 23)
      - Black, Stephen 1972 (Box 23)
      - Blass, Walter 1986 (Box 23)
      - Blau, Shawn 1975 (Box 23)
      - Blumberg, A. J. 1976 (Box 23)
      - Bowden, Lt. Joseph 1973 (Box 23)
      - Bowland, R. A. 1981 (Box 23)
      - Bowlby, J. 1975 (Box 23)
      - Boy Scouts 1972 (Box 23)
      - Bradley, William G. 1984 (Box 23)
      - Braude, Ben 1975 (Box 23)
      - Brink, L. and Olive, D. 1973 (Box 23)
      - Brossard, Rev. Gabriel 1970 (Box 23)
      - Brown, Gov. Edmund G., Jr. 1975 (Box 23)
      - Brown, Rita 1982 (Box 23)
      - Brown, W. K. 1978 (Box 23)
      - Brownstein, L. 1976 (Box 23)
      - Brynjolfssen, Ari 1981 (Box 23)
      - Burkle E, Jorge 1972 (Box 23)
      - Burks, Arthur W. 1976 (Box 23)
      - Bushman, Bruce E. 1975 (Box 23)
      - Bustamente Llaca, Enrique 1979 (Box 23)
      - Buttke, Thomas F. 1987 (Box 23)
      - Byam, Clark R. 1985 (Box 23)
    - Calandra, Alexander 1968-79 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Cambridge University Press, Dirac Memorial Lectures
      - Dirac Memorial Volume (proposed) 1985-86 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Elementary Particles...Dirac Memorial Lectures: Correspondence and documents (folders 18-19) 1986; (folder 20) 1987 (Box 23, Folder Folders 18-20)
      - Edited page proofs 1987 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Weinberg lecture (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Artwork (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Cambridge University Press, book on superstrings 1987 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Cheng, Ta-Pei 1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Clark, Terence 1983-85 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Cornell University, Messenger Lectures (The Character of Physical Law) (folder 7) 1963-66; (folder 8) 1967-86 (Box 24, Folder Folders 7-8)
    - Cortines, Ramon See: Pasadena Unified School District
    - Cowan, Glen See: Ginzburg, V. L.
    - Crick, Francis H. C. 1978-84 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Cushing, James T. 1985 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - C misc (2 folders)
      - Cabrera, Blas 1982 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Cahill, Kevin 1975 (Box 24)
      - Cahn, Bob, and Colglazier, Bill 1973 (Box 24)
      - Cahn, Judah 1983 (Box 24)
      - Calendar, Richard 1975 (Box 24)
      - California Museum of Science and Industry 1973 (Box 24)
      - Caltech Y 1978 (Box 24)
      - Campbell, David 1977 (with photos) (Box 24)
      - Canadian Broadcasting Corporation 1978 (Box 24)
      - Carlisle, E. Fred 1977 (Box 24)
      - Cary, K. 1979 (Box 24)
      - Cassell, Bennett H. 1981 (Box 24)
      - Chacko, Thomas 1974 (Box 24)
      - Challis, L. J. 1974 (Box 24)
      - Chang, Lee 1979-81 (Box 24)
      - Chang, Wen-yu 1981 (Box 24)
      - Chang, W. S. 1973 (Box 24)
      - Channel City Club 1965 (Box 24)
      - Chen, Ning Yang (Frank) 1982 (Box 24)
      - Cheng, Hung 1977 (Box 24)
      - Chou, Pei-yuan 1973 See also: Wu, Yu-hsun (Box 24)
      - Chown, Marcus 1982 (Box 24)
      - Christopherson, Mary L. 1986 (Box 24)
      - Chubatow, George 1974 (Box 24)
      - Cirker, Hayward 1981 (Box 24)
      - Cisneros, Arturo 1984 (Box 24)
      - Clark, J. Kent 1976 (Box 24)
      - Cocconi, Giuseppe 1976-80 See also: Weisskopf, Victor (Box 24)
      - Cohen, David B. 1975 (Box 24)
      - Cohen, Michal 1985 (cryptograph) (Box 24)
      - Colasuona, Gary 1972 (Box 24)
      - Colglazier, William 1972 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Colgrove, R. C. 1978 (Box 24)
      - Collcutt, Bertram 1985 (Box 24)
      - Columbia University 1976 (Box 24)
      - Committee of Concerned Scientists 1975 (Box 24)
      - Contogouris, A. P. 1979 (Box 24)
      - Counts, Richard W. 1978 (Box 24)
      - Coutts, Robert See: Van Nuys High School (Box 24)
      - Cox, Beulah 1975 (Box 24)
      - Crabtree, James H. 1985 (Box 24)
      - Crease, Robert 1985 (Box 24)
      - Cremer, George D. 1975 (Box 24)
      - Creveling, R. A. 1974 (Box 24)
      - Crnkovich, Joseph 1974 (Box 24)
      - Cronin, James W. 1972 (Box 24)
    - Devreese, J. T. 1973-82 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Drell, Sidney 1973-78 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - D misc (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Davis, J. 1979 (Box 24)
      - Davis, Monte 1982 (Box 24)
      - Deb, B. M. 1973 (Box 24)
      - De Martini, F. 1986 (Box 24)
      - Demetriades, Donna 1985 (Box 24)
      - Desert Sun School 1965 (Box 24)
      - Dewdney, A. K. 1982 (Box 24)
      - DeWire, John 1976 (Box 24)
      - Diaz Jimenez, Alfonso 1979 (Box 24)
      - Dickinson, J. Thomas 1985 (Box 24)
      - Dijkhuis, G. C. 1979 (Box 24)
      - Dixon, Paul 1975 (Box 24)
      - Dixson, William 1976 (Box 24)
      - Dodson, Jeffrey 1974 (Box 24)
      - Donnelly, Russell J. 1974 (Box 24)
      - Driessen, Patrick 1980 (Box 24)
      - Dubois, Gregory 1981 (Box 24)
      - DuMond, Jesse 1972 See also: Sections V, VIII (Box 24)
      - Dunham, G. L. 1972 (Box 24)
      - Dyakonov, D. I. 1986 (Box 24)
      - Dychiao, Benito, Jr. 1983 (Box 24)
      - Dy-Liacco, Rafael 1978 (Box 24)
    - Erhard, Werner See: est Foundation
    - Esalen Institute 1974, 1983-86 See also: Sarfatti, J. (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - est Foundation 1977-87 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - E misc (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Edwards, A. W. J. 1975 (Box 25)
      - Ehrlich, Eleanor 1982 (with photo) (Box 25)
      - Einaudi, Giulio, Editore 1978 (Box 25)
      - Elcaness, Harold 1987 (Box 25)
      - Elias, Isidor 1985 (Box 25)
      - Elliott, R. S. 1965 (Box 25)
      - Ellis, Stephen D. 1974 (Box 25)
      - Elser, Veit 1980 (Box 25)
      - Encyclopedia Brittanica 1972 (Box 25)
      - Escobar, Carlos O. 1973 (Box 25)
      - Etheridge, Lloyd S. 1979 (Box 25)
      - Eyges, Trudy 1974 (with photo) (Box 25)
      - Ezawa, Zyun F. 1973 (Box 25)
    - Fox, Geoffrey 1974 See also: Section VIII (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Fritzsch, Harald 1977-78 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - F misc (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Faissner, Helmut 1972 (Box 25)
      - Farber, Yetta 1982 (Box 25)
      - Farmelo, Graham 1975 (Box 25)
      - Feinberg, Jack 1972 (Box 25)
      - Fernandez-Moran, Humberto 1972 (Box 25)
      - Ferreira, Ricardo 1975 (Box 25)
      - Feynman, Carl n.d. Feynman, Debbie 1985 (Box 25)
      - Field, R. D. 1977 See also: Section VIII (Box 25)
      - Finkelstein, David 1975 (Box 25)
      - Fiola, Harvey 1974 (Box 25)
      - Fischbach, E. 1986 (Box 25)
      - Fisher, Michael E. 1977 (Box 25)
      - Fletcher, C. H. 1977 (Box 25)
      - Flynn, Thomas 1979 (Box 25)
      - Ford, Kenneth 1982, 1987 (Box 25)
      - Foundations of Physics 1986 (Box 25)
      - Frank, Evelyn 1973, n.d. (Box 25)
      - Franzini, P. 1973 (Box 25)
      - Frederick, D. E. 1972 (Box 25)
      - Fredkin, E. 1973-74, 1982 (Box 25)
      - Freeman, Gordon 1986 (Box 25)
      - Freinkel, Carol 1975 (Box 25)
      - Frenkel, V. 1972 (Box 25)
      - Frigyes, Sziklai n.d. Frind, A. 1972 (Box 25)
      - Fröhlich, Andreas 1975 (Box 25)
      - Funkhouser, A. J. 1973 (Box 25)
    - Gell-Mann, Murray See: Section II, Nobel Prize, Swedish Royal Academy of Science; Section VIII
    - Ginzburg, V. L. (Glen Cowan) 1971-86 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Goldberger, Marvin See: Section II, Orbisphere Corp.
    - G misc (2 folders)
      - Gale, George 1987 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Garcia, Armando 1985 (Box 25)
      - Garcia, Franco Miralles 1969 (Box 25)
      - Gardner, Ann 1985 (Box 25)
      - Garrett, Anthony 1982 (Box 25)
      - Gelbard, Martin 1983 (Box 25)
      - Genz, H. 1987 (Meyers Grosses Universal- Lexikon) (Box 25)
      - George, Alexander 1975 (Box 25)
      - Gibson, Malcolm 1972 (Box 25)
      - Gilde, Hans-Georg 1974 (Box 25)
      - Gill, Tepper 1977-79 Gillingham, Peter N. 1975 (Box 25)
      - Glashow, Shelly 1979 (Box 25)
      - Gleeson, Austin 1986 (Box 25)
      - Gold, Steven 1972 (Box 25)
      - Gold, Thomas 1972 (Box 25)
      - Goldberg, Irwin See: Gold, Steven (Box 25)
      - Goldin, Fletcher 1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Goldin, Yair 1982 (Box 25)
      - Goldman, Stanford 1976 (Box 25)
      - Goodall, Marcus n.d. (Box 25)
      - Goodstein, David, 1975, n.d. See also: Section VIII (Box 25)
      - Gossick, B. R. 1973 (Box 25)
      - Gottfried, Kurt 1975 (Box 25)
      - Gotzb-Meyer, Z. 1976 (Box 25)
      - Goulianos, Dinos 1980 (Box 25)
      - Gozzi, E. 1982 (Box 25)
      - Graphic Films Corp. See: Novros, Lester (Box 25)
      - Gray, Harry [alias Judge Carter] and Shirley 1978 (Box 25)
      - Greenberg, O. W. and Yodh, G. B. 1974 (Box 25)
      - Griffin, David 1983 (Box 25)
      - Grossberg, Stephen 1983 (Box 25)
      - Guberman, J. 1977-78 Guerrero, Fausto H. 1983 (Box 25)
      - Gunion, John F. 1978, 1982 (Box 25)
    - Hawking, Stephen 1977-78 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Hey, Tony and Jessie 1972, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Hillis, Danny See: Thinking Machines Corporation
    - Hoyle, Sir Fred 1974 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Hughes Aircraft Company 1975-83 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - H misc (2 folders)
      - Hacinliyan, Avadis 1982 (Bogazici University) (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Hagedorn, R. 1976 (Box 25)
      - Halpern, Howard S. 1976 (Box 25)
      - Hamilton, David 1975 (Box 25)
      - Hamilton, Douglas 1978-79 (Box 25)
      - Hamilton, Jim n.d. (Box 25)
      - Hamm, Richard 1979 (Box 25)
      - Hammer, Preston C. 1975 (Box 25)
      - Hamming, R. 1983 (Box 25)
      - Hammond, George 1976 (Box 25)
      - Handler, Sheryl 1984 (Box 25)
      - Hanft, Bernard 1985 (Box 25)
      - Hansma, Paul K. 1985 (Box 25)
      - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich 1972 (Box 25)
      - Harriman, Peter N. 1987 (Box 25)
      - Harris, Jay H. 1976 (Box 25)
      - Hart, Michael H. 1980 (Box 25)
      - Harvey Mudd College 1974-87 (Box 25)
      - Hartle, James B. 1987 (Box 25)
      - Hasty, Ben 1973 (Box 25)
      - Hawkins, David 1975 (Box 25)
      - Hayes, Miles V. 1984 (Box 25)
      - Heaney, Michael B. 1982 (Box 25)
      - Heisenberg, Werner 1976 (Box 25)
      - Heller, Peter 1981 (Box 25)
      - Hellworth, Robert 1974 (Box 25)
      - Henley, Christopher 1978 (Box 25)
      - Henrich, C. J. 1975 (Box 25)
      - Henry, Richard C. 1983 (Box 25)
      - Hetherington, James S. 1960 (Box 25)
      - Heusch, Clemens 1976 (Box 25)
      - Hewlett-Packard 1987 (Box 25)
      - Hibbs, Bart 1972 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Higbie, J. 1975 (Box 25)
      - Hight, Carl 1981 (Box 25)
      - Hill, John J. 1963 (Box 25)
      - Hingert, H. B. 1973 (Box 25)
      - Hinkley, Roy 1984 (Box 25)
      - Hird, Chuck 1985 (Box 25)
      - Hobart, Robert 1972 (Box 25)
      - Hobson, Victor G. 1981 (Box 25)
      - Hoddeson, Lillian 1979 (Box 25)
      - de Hoffman, Frederic 1982 (Box 25)
      - Hofstadter, D. R. 1975-76 (Box 25)
      - Höhler, G. 1974 (Box 25)
      - Honig, William 1973 (Box 25)
      - Hopfield, John See: Landauer, Rolf See also: Section VIII (Box 25)
      - Hora, Heinrich 1986 (Box 25)
      - Horowitz, Alan 1986 (Box 25)
      - Houston, Heidi 1983 (Box 25)
      - Hsu, Chang-pen 1983 (Box 25)
      - Hsu, J. P. 1973 (Box 25)
      - Hu, Ning 1985 (Box 25)
      - Hubbard, J. 1976 (Box 25)
      - Hudár, Andrej 1976 (Box 25)
      - Hudson, John Lee 1983 (Box 25)
      - Huggins, Elisha 1982 (Box 25)
      - Hwa, Rudolph 1973 (Box 25)
      - Hyde, Ron 1974 (Box 25)
    - International Thinking Machines Corporation See: Thinking Machines Corporation
    - Iran, Ministry of Science and Higher Education 1975 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - I misc (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - IBM 1985 (Box 25)
      - Ihinger, Robert 1987 (cryptograph) (Box 25)
      - Imich, Alexander 1987 (Box 25)
      - Indiana University 1974 (Box 25)
      - Ireland, Karin 1987 (Box 25)
      - Irvine, Clyde 1974-75 Isaacson, Michael 1985 (Box 25)
      - Islam, M. M. 1979 (Box 25)
      - Israel Institute of Technology See: Technion (Box 25)
    - Jackiw, Roman 1982-83 See Also: Section VIII (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - J misc (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Jackson, Dave 1975 (Box 25)
      - Jackson, Philip, Jr. 1976 (Box 25)
      - Jacobs, Morris 1987 (Box 25)
      - Jaeger, Janice 1975 (Box 25)
      - Johnson, Carl 1975 (Box 25)
      - Jonas, R. Robert 1972-73 (Box 25)
      - Jordan, Amzie B. 1986 (Box 25)
      - Joseph, John and Pat 1986 (with photo) (Box 25)
      - Juarez, Franklin 1975 (Box 25)
      - Judd, A. Bradford 1986 (Box 25)
      - Julesz, Bela 1977 See also: Section VIII (Box 25)
    - KEK National Laboratory for High Energy Physics [Japan] 1981 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Koji, Tetsu 1979-82 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - K misc (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Kac, Mark 1984 (Box 26)
      - Kamin, O. 1982 (Box 26)
      - Karim, Munawar 1973 (Box 26)
      - Karplus, Robert 1973 (Box 26)
      - Katcoff, David n.d. Katzenstein Associates 1985 (Box 26)
      - Kauffmann, Fred 1973 (Box 26)
      - Kauffmann, Kenneth 1973 (Box 26)
      - KCET 1982 (Box 26)
      - Kee, Richard 1978 (Box 26)
      - Keller, Evelyn Fox 1983 (Box 26)
      - Kemper, G. Kenneth 1985 (Box 26)
      - Kendall, H. W. 1973 (Box 26)
      - Kim, D. Y. 1980 (Box 26)
      - Kish, Andrew W. 1977 (Box 26)
      - Kistiakowsky, Vera 1972 (Box 26)
      - Kittel, W. 1981 (Box 26)
      - Kleinman, David 1979 (Box 26)
      - Klinger, Yehuda 1972 (Box 26)
      - Kounosu, S. 1972 (Box 26)
      - Kovac, Sàndor 1985 (with photo) (Box 26)
      - Krakowski, M. 1965 (Box 26)
      - Kramer, Bruce M. 1980 (Box 26)
      - Krieger, M. H. 1986 (Box 26)
      - Kriegsman, Sali Ann 1975 (Box 26)
      - Krier, Timothy 1977 (Box 26)
      - Krinsky, Sam 1974 (Box 26)
      - Krysac, L. C. 1987 (Box 26)
      - Kumar, T. S. Mohan 1975 (Box 26)
      - Kursunoglu, Behram See: Cambridge University Press, Dirac Memorial Volume (Box 26)
      - Kurti, Susannah and Camilla 1980 (Box 26)
    - Lectro-Media, Ltd. 1978 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Lederman, Leon M. 1981-82 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Lenart, Yvonne 1980 (cryptographic lock) (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - LEX (Language Experience, Experiment & Exchange, with photo) 1987 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - L misc (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Latham, John 1983 (Box 26)
      - Lancaster, Anthony et al. 1976 (Box 26)
      - Landauer, Rolf and Hopfield, John 1982 See also: Section VIII (Box 26)
      - Lasarow, Marilyn 1981 (Box 26)
      - Laufer, A. R. 1976 (Box 26)
      - Lauritsen, Charles and Thomas 1973 (Box 26)
      - Leadstone, G. S. 1986 (Box 26)
      - Lee, Benjamin W. 1972-73 (Box 26)
      - Lee, Mary D. (Box 26)
      - Lefebvre, Vladimir 1983 (Box 26)
      - Lehmkuhl, Egon 1975 (Box 26)
      - Leighton, Robert B. 1974, n.d. (Box 26)
      - Lentz, Harris 1975 (Box 26)
      - Leonard, Marston C. 1974 (Box 26)
      - Lessard, Amos J. 1983 (Box 26)
      - Leuliette, Eric W. 1984 (Box 26)
      - Levin, Max 1977 (Box 26)
      - Lewis, Rodney 1981 (Box 26)
      - Liberman, David 19974 (Box 26)
      - Light Impressions 1986 (with holograms) (Box 26)
      - Linnebach, Egbert 1982 (Box 26)